Foto por definir

JAVA DEVELOPER

ADDRESS: Cr 40 #66C-32 APTO 201

CITY: Medellín-Ant.

DATE OF BIRTH: 27/02/1991

MARITAL STATUS: Single

NATIONALITY: Colombian

+57 3113590047

pablohincapie@hotmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/pablo-andreshincapie-duque-39b96215b/

https://github.com/pablohincapie

https://pablohincapie.github.io/home/

PABLO ANDRÉS

HINCAPIÉ DUQUE

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nov 2018 - Present » Software Developer | Quipux

- Modifies existing software to correct bugs, upgrade interfaces and improve performance.
- Develops software modules based on customer's requirements.
- Works closely with customers to efficiently resolve issues.

May 2015 - Nov 2018» Systems Analyst | Konecta

- -Performed all software development life cycle activities from preliminary analysis to deployment. Coded unit tests with the porpuse of eliminating application errors.
- Maintained a system for documenting code and keeping track of software developments.
- Participated in creating scalable systems for three primary departments, incluiding human resources, marketing and supply chain.
- -Helped write code for a website update using html tools.

Jan 2013 - Jun 2013 » Developer | Ordenamientos Profesionales Automatizados (OPA)

- -Developed and designed software programs for financial tracking and reporting optimized user effectiveness by creating a detailed process of accounting.
- -Development and to track chenges made in existig programs using mathematical to design software.

Jan 2012- Jun 2012 »

- System Internship | Clofan Clinic
- Maintaining networks, servers and security programs and systems.
- -Upgrading and installation of new hardware and software, backup data and create and change passwords.

EDUCATION

2012 » System Technologist Metropolitan Technological Institute(ITM)

2014 » Computer Science Engineer Metropolitan Technological Institute(ITM)

PROFILE

software engineer with experience and passion for developing innovate programs that expedite the efficiency and effectiveness of organizational success mainly Java frameworks. Well- versed in technology and writing code to create systems that are reliable and user-friendly. Loves working on passionate about learning new challenging, technologies working and in teams.

COURSES

Present

Feb 2018 - » English Language Colombo Americano Center | Medellín

Oct 2013

applications development with design and layout Sena | Medellín

SKILLS

JavaScript

Jquery

PHP

CSS

Git

HTML5



JAVA



SQL



Maven



Junit



Hibernate



Spring **JDBC**



REFERENCES

- Jessica Martinez Orozco Phone +57 3146745620
- Duban Bedoya Phone +57 3127882280
- Bibiana Hincapié Phone +57 3107984863

APTITUDES / INTERESTS















LANGUAGES

English | Intermediate level